Like someone can be a completely nice guy, that doesn't mean that you all have great chemistry.
Someone can be a good guy and it doesn't mean that you all have chemistry.
None of these things should determine whether or not you have to give somebody a chance.
At the end of the day, do y'all mesh? Do y'all click?
And do you have healing in your own space to even be able to take in a good guy?
Huh? Because that's the other part.
When I see the nice guys finish last rhetoric, I say to myself,
who are the nice guys hollering at?
I don't know about y'all, but I feel like I be seeing nice guys always trying to holler at the bad guys.
The nice guys are trying to get the city girls.
City girls don't want you. They can't even accept you.
They've got too much going on in their intentions, in their trauma, etc.
to even pay attention to you, let alone the good guys.